A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Administration and Officers Files, Office Files of Lonnie Sherrod FA1792
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications, 1964-1987; 8; 9.89 Cubic Feet 28 containers
  - Social Biology Volume 32, 1-4 Spring-Winter Index, Contents (Microfilm shipped to Dr. Sherrod at SSRC), 1985 (Box 58)
  - Television and Social Behavior: Reports and Papers, Volumes I-V, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 136, Box 60, Folder 417, Box 61, Folder 418-420)
  - Television and Growing Up: The Impact of Televised Violence: Report to the Surgeon General United States Public Health Service, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 421)
  - Violence on Television: Hearings Before the Subcommittee on Communications of the Committee on Commerce United States Senate, 1974 April 3-5 (Box 61, Folder 422)
  - Surgeon General's Report by the Scientific Advisory Committee on Television and Social Behavior, Appendix A - Hearings Before the Subcommittee on Communications of the Committee on Commerce United States Senate, 1972 March 21-24 (Box 62, Folder 423)
  - Life Course Dynamics, Glen H. Edler, Jr., 1985 (Box 62, Folder 424-427)
  - Preventive Intervention in Schizophrenia: Are We Ready?, National Institute of Mental Health, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 428)
  - Clinical Infant Intervention Research Programs: Selected Overview and Discussion, National Institute of Mental Health, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 429)
  - A Guide to Evaluating Prevention Programs in Mental Health, National Institute of Mental Health, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 430)
  - Child Development, Volume 39, Number 4, Society for Research in Child Development, 1968 December (Box 63, Folder 431)
  - Some Child-Rearing Antecedents of Aggression and Dependency in Young Children, Genetic Psychology Monographs, 47, 135-234, Laboratory of Human Development, Harvard University, R.R. Sears, J.W.M. Whiting, V. Nowlis, and P.S. Sears, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 432)
  - Mental Health Statistical Note No. 162, Residential Treatment Centers for Emotionally Disturbed Children, United States, 1977-78 and 1979-80, 1983 August (Box 63, Folder 433)
  - Psychological Sciences Division 1984 Programs, Office of Naval Research, Arlington, Virginia, 1984 December (Box 63, Folder 434)
  - Mental Health, United States, U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, Public Health Service, Alcohol, Drug Abuse, and Mental Health Administration, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 435)
  - Schizophrenia Bulletin, National Institute of Mental Health, Volume 7, Number 1, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 436)
  - Disadvantaged Children and Their First School Experiences, ETC-Head Start Longitudinal Study, Structure and Development of Personal-Social Behaviors in Preschool Settings, Walter Emmerich, 1971 November (Box 63, Folder 437)
  - Television and Human Behavior: A Guide to the Pertinent Schientific Literature, Prepared Under a Grant from the Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, George Comstock and Marilyn Fisher, 1975 June (Box 64, Folder 438)
  - Television and Human Behavior: The Research Horizon, Future and Present, Prepared Under a Grant from the Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, George Comstock and Geor Lindsey, 1975 June (Box 64, Folder 439)
  - Television and Human Behavior: The Key Studies, Prepared Under a Grant from the Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, George Comstock, 1975 June (Box 64, Folder 440)
  - Teaching Children How to Think: Synthesis, Interpretation, and Evaluation of Research and Devleopment of Creative Problem Solving, John F. Feldhusen et. al., 1975 March (Box 64, Folder 441)